Tufts Observer UP055
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Observer, 1983 -- 1984; UP055.015; 1 Volumes
  This series consists of bound volumes of the Tufts Observer newspaper, dated from September 9, 1983 to May 20, 1984. In 1969, the Observer replaced the Tufts Weekly as the weekly student-published paper. Observer states that its objective is to be 'the newspaper of record' for Tufts University. The Observer covers current events and university news and sports. Typical features include editorials and opinion pieces, a calendar of events, art and culture articles, creative works, and comics.
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-09-09; UP055.015.015.00001 (Box 15)
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-09-16; UP055.015.015.00002 (Box 15)
    [Advising] Revised systems proposed. p. 5.
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-09-23; UP055.015.015.00003 (Box 15)
    Academic Freedom 1983. The Progressive examines academic freedom at Tufts; [American association of University professors] Recommends modified retirement plans; [American association of University professors] Tufts, AAUP approved part-time professor motion, editorial
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-09-30; UP055.015.015.00004 (Box 15)
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-10-07; UP055.015.015.00005 (Box 15)
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-10-14; UP055.015.015.00006 (Box 15)
    [Academic Honesty] Senate considers honor system pp. 5, 20; Activities and Organizations, 1983-84. Funds frozen for groups.
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-10-21; UP055.015.015.00007 (Box 15)
    [Alcohol Abuse 1983-84] WFNX and Tufts fight drunk driving; Editorial.
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-10-28; UP055.015.015.00008 (Box 15)
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-11-04; UP055.015.015.00009 (Box 15)
    [Admissions, Office of, 1983-84] Tufts to admit more Boston applicants.
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-11-11; UP055.015.015.00010 (Box 15)
    Ronald Brinn new director of alumni relations [includes photo]; Academic Freedom and Tenure 1983-84. Student/faculty committee established new tenure procedure. [Alumni 1983-84] Brinn, Ronald C., new director of alumni relations, p. 5, 23.
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-11-18; UP055.015.015.00011 (Box 15)
    [Aesthetic Decisions] Artists in intimate atmosphere, p. 19.
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-12-02; UP055.015.015.00012 (Box 15)
    [Aesthetic Decisions] Letter re all college 191 course, p. 9.
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-12-09; UP055.015.015.00013 (Box 15)
    Academic Calendar 1983. Approved through 1988; Academic Calendar 1983. Editorial.
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-01-27; UP055.015.015.00014 (Box 15)
    [Administration] Durgin, William, Vice President for finance resigns (photo). p. 4. [Alcohol Abuse] New drinking policy proposed. Editorial.
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-02-03; UP055.015.015.00015 (Box 15)
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-02-10; UP055.015.015.00016 (Box 15)
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-02-17; UP055.015.015.00017 (Box 15)
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-02-24; UP055.015.015.00018 (Box 15)
    [Admissions, Office of, 1984] Tufts attracts more applicants.
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-03-02; UP055.015.015.00019 (Box 15)
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-03-09; UP055.015.015.00020 (Box 15)
    [Alcohol Abuse] Hammond (Edward) tells frats and clubs about liquor liabilities.
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-03-15; UP055.015.015.00021 (Box 15)
  - Tufts Observer, March 32, 1984-04-01; UP055.015.015.00022 (Box 15)
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-04-06; UP055.015.015.00023 (Box 15)
    [American chemical society] Chemistry society mixes business and pleasure; [Alumni council] Twelve senior awards recipients named; Brett Ackerman (1987). Freshmen start Promotions delivery service (photo); [Ad Hoc committee to review tenure process] Tenure report discussed (photos) p. 1,22. Committee reports to senate, p. 5, 21; Activities and Organizations, 1984. Chemistry society mixes business and pleasure.
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-04-13; UP055.015.015.00024 (Box 15)
    [Allen, Charles] Nazi hunter condems U.S. use of war criminals in government.
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-04-20; UP055.015.015.00025 (Box 15)
    [Advising] Mayer acts as advisor. p. 5. Pressures alleviated. p. 5. [Allocations Board] Proposes 1984-85 budget.
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-04-27; UP055.015.015.00026 (Box 15)
    [Admissions, Office of, 1984] Protests exclusion from Admissions Fair.
  - Tufts Observer; Commencement Issue, 1984-05-20; UP055.015.015.00027 (Box 15)
    [Ad Hoc committee to review tenure process] Faculty wavers ad hoc proposal. p. 3, 5.; [Administration] Deanship awaits approval. p. 4.
- Tufts Observer, 1984 -- 1985; UP055.016; 1 Volumes
  This series consists of bound volumes of the Tufts Observer newspaper, dated from August 31, 1984 to May 17, 1985. In 1969, the Observer replaced the Tufts Weekly as the weekly student-published paper. Observer states that its objective is to be 'the newspaper of record' for Tufts University. The Observer covers current events and university news and sports. Typical features include editorials and opinion pieces, a calendar of events, art and culture articles, creative works, and comics.
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-08-31; UP055.016.016.00001 (Box 16)
    [Administration] New Dean of Administration: Lawrence Ladd. p. 3.; [Adulyadej, Bhumibol (King of Thailand)] Mayer to present honorary degree to King of Thailand. p. 2.
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-09-07; UP055.016.016.00002 (Box 16)
    [Alumni 1984-85] Alumni recurited for media appeals board, p. 3.
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-09-14; UP055.016.016.00003 (Box 16)
    [Admissions, Office of, 1984-85] Field representatives provide student view of Tufts.
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-09-21; UP055.016.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-09-28; UP055.016.016.00005 (Box 16)
    [Academic Honesty] Faculty discusses academic ethics pp. 3, 5; [Ad Hoc committee to review tenure process] Letter re: faculty vote on committee report. P.7.
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-10-05; UP055.016.016.00006 (Box 16)
    [Afro-American Cultural Center] Letter critical of article on Afro-American Center, p. 9, 10.
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-10-12; UP055.016.016.00007 (Box 16)
    [Afro-American Cultural Center] Letter responding to criticisms of Observer article, p. 8.
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-10-19; UP055.016.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-10-26; UP055.016.016.00009 (Box 16)
    [Ad Hoc committee on liberal Arts-Jackson] Educational policy committee recommends intellectual risk taking. p. 3, 4.
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-11-02; UP055.016.016.00010 (Box 16)
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-11-09; UP055.016.016.00011 (Box 16)
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-11-16; UP055.016.016.00012 (Box 16)
    [Advanced Anatomy] Students go from bullfrogs to bodies in OT labs. p. 19.
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-11-30; UP055.016.016.00013 (Box 16)
  - Tufts Observer, 1984-12-07; UP055.016.016.00014 (Box 16)
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-01-25; UP055.016.016.00015 (Box 16)
    [Admissions, Office of, 1985] Behnke accepts position at MIT (photo); [American association of University professors] Tufts, AAUP make salary recommendations
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-02-01; UP055.016.016.00016 (Box 16)
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-02-08; UP055.016.016.00017 (Box 16)
    [Admissions, Office of, 1985] Drop in transfer admission.
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-02-15; UP055.016.016.00018 (Box 16)
    [Adler, Spencer] Creates menagerie of ingenuity (photo). p. 21.
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-02-22; UP055.016.016.00019 (Box 16)
    [Alumni lecture series] Astronaut alumnus Frederick Hauck [A1962] speaks at Tufts [includes photo]; [Admissions, Director of, 1985] Job search almost complete.
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-03-01; UP055.016.016.00020 (Box 16)
    [Alumni/ae] Network to strengthen Tufts bonds; [Admissions, Office of, 1985] Black applicants receive extension. Editorial; [Alpha Tau Omega] Greek like with a twist [photo]
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-03-08; UP055.016.016.00021 (Box 16)
    [Academic Honesty] Observation on cheating p. 11; [Afro-American Society] Afro-American Society sponsored speaker receives threats, p. 1, 25.
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-03-29; UP055.016.016.00022 (Box 16)
    [Ad Hoc Committee Against Institutionalized Racism] Changes demanded in racial policies pp. 1, 21, Editorial p. 8, Letter re: racism p. 8. [ALlocations Board] Allocations released.
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-04-05; UP055.016.016.00023 (Box 16)
    [Ad Hoc Committee Against Institutionalized Racism] Anti racism petition to circulate. pp. 3, 23; [Advising] Mentor advising proposed. p .2.
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-04-12; UP055.016.016.00024 (Box 16)
    [Amalgamates] A cappella coeds create harmonious chords [includes photo]; [Alumni association] New tradition: Tuftonia's day; [Ad Hoc Committee Against Institutionalized Racism] Anti racism petition to circulate. pp. 3, 23; [Advising] Mentor advising proposed. p .2.
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-04-19; UP055.016.016.00025 (Box 16)
    [Alumni/ae] Tuftonia's day trivia
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-04-26; UP055.016.016.00026 (Box 16)
    [Admissions, Office of, 1985] Black applicants down 6%. [Ad Hoc Committee Against Institutionalized Racism] Ballou sit-in enters third day (photo). pp. 1, 27, Editorial p. 12; [Ad Hoc Committee Against Institutionalized Racism] Police infiltrate meeting? pp. 1, 31. [al-Hussein, Queen Noor] Advocates peace plan.
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-05-17; UP055.016.016.00027 (Box 16)
    Activities - Organizations, 1985. Treasures of Tufts hard to find.
- Tufts Observer, 1985 -- 1986; UP055.017; 1 Volumes
  This series consists of bound volumes of the Tufts Observer newspaper, dated from August 30, 1985 to May 18, 1986. In 1969, the Observer replaced the Tufts Weekly as the weekly student-published paper. The Observer states that its objective is to be 'the newspaper of record' for Tufts University. The Observer covers current events and university news and sports. Typical features include editorials and opinion pieces, a calendar of events, art and culture articles, creative works, and comics.
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-08-30; UP055.017.017.00001 (Box 17)
    [Administration] Seven picked to fill vacant posts: R. Miles Uhrig, Pamela Allara, Rosemarie Van Camp, David Lundberg, John Darcy, Rosemarie Rogers, Jeanne Dillon, pp. 2, 4. Gustavo Alfaro (prof. of romance languages) Named acting department chairman of Romance Languages. Pamela Allara (administration) Named associate dean of the Museum School program.
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-09-06; UP055.017.017.00002 (Box 17)
    [Admissions, Office of, 1985-86] Administrations clarifies contradicting figures of Black enrollment.
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-09-20; UP055.017.017.00003 (Box 17)
    [American association of University professors] [Accuracy in Academia] Causes AAUP [American Association of University Professors] concern. pp. 5, 23; [Admissions, Office of] Search for dean begins anew. p. 2.
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-09-27; UP055.017.017.00004 (Box 17)
    [Alumni/ae] Possible alumni club to be established
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-10-04; UP055.017.017.00005 (Box 17)
    [Academic Honesty] Assessment of campus cheating pp. 1, 23
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-10-11; UP055.017.017.00006 (Box 17)
    [ACOIL] Promotes intellectual life beyond class, p 19; Students avoid AIA [Accuracy in Academia] p. 3; [Accuracy in Academia] Editorial p. 8
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-10-18; UP055.017.017.00007 (Box 17)
    AIA [Accuracy in Academia] contacts Primary Source. p. 2; Letter re: AIA [Accuracy in Academia] / Primary Source p. 10
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-10-25; UP055.017.017.00008 (Box 17)
    [Alumni 1985] Letter re social policy effect on homecoming, p. 8. [Alumni 1985] Seniors show spirit with off-campus float, p. 20. [Alumni 1985] Football and field hockey host homecoming, p. 27.
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-11-01; UP055.017.017.00009 (Box 17)
    [AIDS] Provokes concern. pp. 1, 25.
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-11-08; UP055.017.017.00010 (Box 17)
    [American association of University professors] AAUP calls for Tufts and pension fund divestment
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-11-15; UP055.017.017.00011 (Box 17)
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-11-22; UP055.017.017.00012 (Box 17)
    [Ad Hoc Committee Against Institutionalized Racism] Protestors reiterate demands. pp. 1, 5. Editorial p. 8.
  - Tufts Observer, 1985-12-06; UP055.017.017.00013 (Box 17)
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-01-24; UP055.017.017.00014 (Box 17)
    [American association of University professors] AAUP chapter calls for TIAA/CREF divestment; [Ad Hoc Committee Against Institutionalized Racism] Activists to protest Nazis, KKK in Philadelphia. pp. 3, 22
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-01-31; UP055.017.017.00015 (Box 17)
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-02-07; UP055.017.017.00016 (Box 17)
    Toshiko Akiyoshi excites All That Jazz (photo).
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-02-14; UP055.017.017.00017 (Box 17)
    [American association of University professors] Discusses salaries
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-02-21; UP055.017.017.00018 (Box 17)
    [Afro-American Cultural Center] Racism at Tufts discussed, p. 3, 4.
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-02-28; UP055.017.017.00019 (Box 17)
    [Administration] Receives computer system. p. 5; [Aerobics in Harmony] Freshman Charles Denegal leads aerobic workout (photo), p. 23.
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-03-07; UP055.017.017.00020 (Box 17)
    [Admissions, Office of] Tufts appoints new dean of admissions, David Cuttino. p. 1.
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-03-14; UP055.017.017.00021 (Box 17)
    [Admissions, Office of] Tufts appoints new dean of admissions, David Cuttino. pp. 1, 25.; [Advisory Committee on Research] Faculty debates SDI. pp. 3, 21.
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-03-28; UP055.017.017.00022 (Box 17)
    [Administration] Academic Audits [1985;1986]. Departments undergo academic audits.; Academic Audit [1[Advisory Committee on Faculty Research Support and Facilities] Advisory committee seeks input. pp. 3, 14. [Allocations Board] Releases funding figures.
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-04-04; UP055.017.017.00023 (Box 17)
    [Aga Khan, Sadruddin] Recipient of honorary doctor of humane letters degree, p. 11.
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-04-11; UP055.017.017.00024 (Box 17)
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-04-18; UP055.017.017.00025 (Box 17)
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-05-18; UP055.017.017.00026 (Box 17)
- Tufts Observer, 1986; UP055.018; 1 Volumes
  This series consists of bound volumes of the Tufts Observer newspaper, dated from August 29, 1986 to December 5, 1986. In 1969, the Observer replaced the Tufts Weekly as the weekly student-published paper. The Observer states that its objective is to be 'the newspaper of record' for Tufts University. The Observer covers current events and university news and sports. Typical features include editorials and opinion pieces, a calendar of events, art and culture articles, creative works, and comics.
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-08-29; UP055.018.018.00001 (Box 18)
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-09-05; UP055.018.018.00002 (Box 18)
    [Admissions, Office of] New dean hopes to build diversity at Tufts (photo). p. 2. [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Medford resident complain about AEPi letter.
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-09-12; UP055.018.018.00003 (Box 18)
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-09-19; UP055.018.018.00004 (Box 18)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Lawyers to seek solution. ACOIL (Advisory Committee on Intellectual Life) [Tufts president, Jean] Mayer lectures on education in America. pp 1, 23
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-09-26; UP055.018.018.00005 (Box 18)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] AEPi/Medford at odds over liscense, Councilman supports AEPi.
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-10-03; UP055.018.018.00006 (Box 18)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] AEPi to see judge.
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-10-10; UP055.018.018.00007 (Box 18)
    [Alcohol Abuse] Student hospitalized. [Alpha Epsilon Pi] AEPi looses in court; [American association of University students] Mayer addresses AAUS
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-10-17; UP055.018.018.00008 (Box 18)
    AIDS pp. 1, 24; [American association of University students] Conference addresses area issues
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-10-24; UP055.018.018.00009 (Box 18)
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-10-31; UP055.018.018.00010 (Box 18)
    [Alcohol Abuse] Alcohol poisonings reported.
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-11-07; UP055.018.018.00011 (Box 18)
    AIDS pp. 5, 18.
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-11-14; UP055.018.018.00012 (Box 18)
    Acme Printing (1986-87). Continued expansion planned. [Alcohol Abuse] Committee on Student Life forms subcommittees.
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-11-21; UP055.018.018.00013 (Box 18)
    AIDS pp. 5, 24. [Alcohol Abuse] CSL seeks funds for alcohol counselor. [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Critisized by local [Medford] residents.
  - Tufts Observer, 1986-12-05; UP055.018.018.00014 (Box 18)
- Tufts Observer, 1987; UP055.019; 1 Volumes
  This series consists of bound volumes of the Tufts Observer newspaper, dated from January 23, 1987 to May 17, 1987. In 1969, the Observer replaced the Tufts Weekly as the weekly student-published paper. The Observer states that its objective is to be 'the newspaper of record' for Tufts University. The Observer covers current events and university news and sports. Typical features include editorials and opinion pieces, a calendar of events, art and culture articles, creative works, and comics.
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-01-23; UP055.019.019.00001 (Box 19)
    Steinem to give key address. [Alpha Epsilon Pi] BSOT intended for AEPi house.
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-01-30; UP055.019.019.00002 (Box 19)
    Adams, Douglas; Songwriter performs at Ziggy's, p. 11. [Alpha Epsilon Pi] CSL and Dean of Students discuss differences which include one discipline action re: fraternity.
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-02-06; UP055.019.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-02-13; UP055.019.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-02-20; UP055.019.019.00005 (Box 19)
    [American flag] Flag ceremony considered; Complaint filed against two student pledges of Delta Upsilon for causing disturbances and posing as Observer reporters. [Brian Aalto] pp. 3,12.
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-02-27; UP055.019.019.00006 (Box 19)
    [Admissions] Acceptances sent out early. p. 2. TCU Senate urges hiring of minority recruiter. p. 2.
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-03-06; UP055.019.019.00007 (Box 19)
    Delta Upsilon absolved of charges. [ Brian Aalto] pp. 3,14
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-03-27; UP055.019.019.00008 (Box 19)
    ACME Printing Co. (1987). Tufts science center progressing at former site of ACME Printing Co. [AIDS] condoms, p. 4. [Allocations Board] Raises activity fee.
  - Tufts Observer, April Fool's Day, 1987-04-01; UP055.019.019.00009 (Box 19)
    Beastie Boys Headline Fling
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-04-03; UP055.019.019.00010 (Box 19)
    Senate allocates extra funding for senior week.
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-04-10; UP055.019.019.00011 (Box 19)
    Abi-Saab on role of international law [ Georges Abi-Saab] no. 10 p. 3; [Afro-American Cultural Center] Feature on Afro-American president, p. 2, 6.
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-04-17; UP055.019.019.00012 (Box 19)
    CSL [Committee on Student Life] upholds privacy violation pp. 1,14. Academic Advising [1987]. New program available.; [Academic Resource Center] New program available; p.13. [Admissions, Office of] 3300 candidates chosen. p. 3.
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-04-24; UP055.019.019.00013 (Box 19)
    Anti-Racist Meeting Fizzles
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-05-17; UP055.019.019.00014 (Box 19)
- Tufts Observer, 1987 -- 1988; UP055.020; 1 Volumes
  This series consists of bound volumes of the Tufts Observer newspaper, dated from September 4, 1987 to May 20, 1988. In 1969, the Observer replaced the Tufts Weekly as the weekly student-published paper. The Observer states that its objective is to be 'the newspaper of record' for Tufts University. The Observer covers current events and university news and sports. Typical features include editorials and opinion pieces, a calendar of events, art and culture articles, creative works, and comics.
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-09-04; UP055.020.020.00001 (Box 20)
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-09-11; UP055.020.020.00002 (Box 20)
    [Admissions] Minority recruiters grapple with admissions. p. 3. [Alcohol Task Force] Alcoholism: it can be stopped.
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-09-18; UP055.020.020.00003 (Box 20)
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-09-25; UP055.020.020.00004 (Box 20)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Plans rush.
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-10-02; UP055.020.020.00005 (Box 20)
    [AIDS] p. 2.
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-10-09; UP055.020.020.00006 (Box 20)
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-10-16; UP055.020.020.00007 (Box 20)
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-10-23; UP055.020.020.00008 (Box 20)
    [African-American Center] Lisa Radcliffe, new president of African-American Center, p. 2.
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-10-30; UP055.020.020.00009 (Box 20)
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-11-06; UP055.020.020.00010 (Box 20)
    [Ad Hoc Committee on Fraternities and Sororities] Committee debates Greek roles. pp. 1 ,3; [After Hours] New campus store opens, p. 1, 3.; [AIDS] symposium. p. 2. [Airplane Game] 'Airplane" scam uncovered [editorial].
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-11-13; UP055.020.020.00011 (Box 20)
    [Airplane Game] "Airplane" scan uncovered [editorial].
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-11-20; UP055.020.020.00012 (Box 20)
    [Ad Hoc Committee on Fraternities and Sororities] Gittleman, IGC [InterGreek Council] discuss Greek guidelines. (photo) pp. 1, 11.; [Admissions] Tufts 25th choosiest. pp. 1, 3; [After Hours] Running Smoothly, p. 2.
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-12-04; UP055.020.020.00013 (Box 20)
    [Ad Hoc Committee on Fraternities and Sororities] Gittleman, IGC [InterGreek Council] discuss Greek guidelines. (photo) pp. 1, 11.
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-12-11; UP055.020.020.00014 (Box 20)
    [African-American Center] New director sought, p. 1.
  - Tufts Observer, 1987-01-29; UP055.020.020.00015 (Box 20)
  - Tufts Observer, 1988-02-05; UP055.020.020.00016 (Box 20)
    [Admissions] Minority enrollment increases. pp. 1, 10; [Affirmative Action] minority pitch paying off, p. 1, 10.
  - Tufts Observer, 1988-02-12; UP055.020.020.00017 (Box 20)
  - Tufts Observer, 1988-02-19; UP055.020.020.00018 (Box 20)
    [Affirmative Action] Action audited, p. 1, 3.
  - Tufts Observer, 1988-02-26; UP055.020.020.00019 (Box 20)
    AIESEC [L'Association Internationale des Etudiants en Sciences Economique et Commerciales] A practical Education, p 2; Chinua Achebe speaks at Tufts. p. 2. [Akbar, Na'im] Addresses alienation. [Allocations Board] Tom Pullen looks ahead.
  - Tufts Observer, 1988-03-04; UP055.020.020.00020 (Box 20)
  - Tufts Observer, 1988-03-11; UP055.020.020.00021 (Box 20)
  - Tufts Observer, 1988-04-01; UP055.020.020.00022 (Box 20)
    [Administration] Administration reacts to rape. pp. 1, 3; Rotberg meets with AAUP
  - Tufts Observer, 1988-04-08; UP055.020.020.00023 (Box 20)
  - Tufts Observer, 1988-04-15; UP055.020.020.00024 (Box 20)
  - Tufts Observer, 1988-04-22; UP055.020.020.00025 (Box 20)
    [Alumni association] Outstanding seniors to be recognized with seniors awards; Recipient of Seniors Award, 1988, [David E. Able] p. 2; [Ad Hoc Committee on Fraternities and Sororities] Future of fraternities at Tufts. pp. 1, 13, Editorial p. 4. [Allocations Board] Other ALBO changes explained; MassPIRG budget increase raises questions.
  - Tufts Observer, 1988-04-29; UP055.020.020.00026 (Box 20)
    [Admissions] Minority enrollment increases. pp. 1, 13. Editorial. p. 4; [Affirmative Action] Minority pitch paying off, p. 1, 13; Editorial, p. 4; [African-American Center] Jewell Bell, selected temporary director, p. 2. [Allocations Board] Refused "Roots" funding: editorial; Controversy erupts over new unrecognized publication.
  - Tufts Observer, 1988-05-20; UP055.020.020.00027 (Box 20)
    [American association of University professors] Open letter from AAUP; [Administration] Open letter from AAUP [American Association of University Professors] p. 6.; Tufts Administration Building nears completion. p. 2.
- Tufts Observer, 1988 -- 1990; UP055.021; 1 Volumes; 1 Digital Object(s)